(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-29T06:14:04.009849",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あれ？
Huh?
みんなー！見える？聞こえるー？
Hey everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
やっほー！お誕生日
Yahoo! Happy birthday...
おめでとう！ありがとうね！
Oh, thank you very much!
え、なんか今日は、ここでライブをしに来たんだけど、誕生日だからね。
Um, today I came here to do a live stream, since it's my birthday, you know.
でもなんか、運営さんに事務所に来いって言われて、ここにきました。
But management told me to come to the office, so I came here.
あのー、なんで呼ばれたんでしょうか？
Um, why was I called here, I wonder?
今、運営さんから、なんかこうねクイズを用意してきたから、それに答え頼ないとライブさせてくれないみたいです。
Management prepared some "Korone quizzes" for me, and if I don't answer them, they won't let me stream!
なんやねん！
What the heck?!
え、クイズを？
A quiz?
こ、あ、あ、なるほどね。
Ah, I see, I see.
じゃあこれ4択で答えていく感じね？
So I have to answer from four choices, right?
あ、じゃあ簡単だなこれ。あ、光るちゃんと見て！ほい！ほい！ほい！ほい！ほい！
Ah, then this is easy. Hey, look at the lights properly! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
なに遊んでいって…なんか準備しとるっぽい。
Why am I just playing around... Looks like they're preparing something.
え、これは全問正解とかあるんですか？
Huh, is there a rule where I have to get all of them right?
あ、なんか全問正解しないとライブやっちゃダメなんだって。
Ah, apparently if I don't get all of them right, I can't do my live stream.
あ、8人のメンバーからクイズを募集してきたから、それに全問正解しないとダメっぽい。
Ah, they gathered quizzes from 8 members, so I guess I have to get all of them right.
ライブしに来たのに！
Even though I came here to do a live stream!
え、これま、準備できました？
Um, is it ready?
あ、よし！じゃあ、早速！
Ah, alright! Then, let's get right into it!
行くよ。あ、なんかね、こうねに関するクイズだって、しかも。
Here we go. Oh, and it's a quiz about Korone herself, apparently!
え、簡単じゃんね！じゃあ第1問目！考えてこいよ！
Huh, that's easy! Then, question number one! Think carefully!
なになみ？ころねのTwitterで「場所」という項目に記入している言葉はなんでしょう？
What's this? "What word does Korone write in the 'Location' field on Twitter?"
こんな簡単じゃん！え、悪のエッグマンランド、DOOMのDOOG、
This is so easy! Um, "Evil Eggman Land", "DOOM's DOOG",
MOTHERオネット、にゃんぴょうのフエマイスター。
"MOTHER Onett", "Nyanpyou's Fuemeister".
これは
This is...
かてぃ！え、4の「にゃんぴょうのフエマイスター」！
Kati! Um, number 4, "Nyanpyou's Fuemeister"!
やったー！ありがたー！
Yay! Thank you so much!
え、こんな簡単だよみんな！簡単だよね！
Hey, this is so easy, everyone! It's easy, right?
正解です！
Correct!
え、ふぶきちゃんありがとね！ころねのためにクイズ考えてくれたんだ！ありがと！ありがと！
Fubuki-chan, thank you! You thought of a quiz for Korone! Thank you, thank you!
じゃあ第2問目！早すぎ！早すぎるかな？
Then, question number 2! Too fast! Is it too fast?
第2問目いっちゃおやん！じゃあ第2問ください！
Let's go to the second question! Please give me the second question!
なんだこれ？このサムネイルのは何の配信の時のサムネイルでしょうか？
What is this? "What stream is this thumbnail from?"
あ、じゃあこれ覚えるよこれ！マリンりんか。
Ah, let's memorize this! Marine-rin, huh.
これわね、こね覚えてます。え、おかくろ雑談、おかくろ対戦ゲーム、おかくろ歌、おかくろホラーゲーム。これは4番の「おかくろホラーゲーム」のサムネイルです！
I remember this. Um, "Okakuro Chat", "Okakuro VS Game", "Okakuro Song", "Okakuro Horror Game". This is the thumbnail for #4, "Okakuro Horror Game"!
やったー！
Yay!
にゃにゃにゃにゃ、ありがとー！ありがとー！
Nyan nyan nyan, thank you! Thank you!
これは結構覚えてて、おかゆとね、二人で一緒にね、あの
I remember this pretty well. Okayu and I, together, you know...
リアルでね、リアルってオフコラボでね、ホラーゲームした時のサムネイルです。ころねの手書きです。
in real life—well, in an off-collab—when we played a horror game, that's the thumbnail. It's Korone's handwriting!
ああ楽しいな。クイズなんて、あ、マリンありがとね、クイズ考えてくれて。嬉しい！
Ah, this is fun. A quiz... Ah, Marine, thank you for thinking up a quiz. I'm so happy!
なんかサムネイルとか遡ってくれたのかな。え、なんかコメントもいっぱいありがとう！いっぱいありがとうね！
Did you look back through the thumbnails? And thank you so much for all the comments! Thank you so much!
ありがとう！ポチポチありがとうー！嬉しい！
Thank you! Click-click, thank you! I'm so happy!
じゃあ次の問題いこうかな。じゃあ第3問！
Well then, let's go to the next question. Question number 3!
お願いします！
Please!
え！？スバルがころねに密かに憧れている点は？え、スバルちゃん！？
Huh?! What point does Subaru secretly admire Korone for? Eh, Subaru-chan?!
えー、体力はスバルちゃんあるしな。
Hmm, Subaru-chan has stamina, though.
ゲーム愛もスバルちゃんあるしな。
Subaru-chan has a love for games too.
女子力もスバルちゃんあるしな。
Subaru-chan has girlish charm too.
え、難しい！これちょっといきなり難しくなった！
Eh, hard! This suddenly got difficult!
え、なんだろう？これなんだと思うみんな？
Eh, what could it be? What do you guys think this is?
全部？あ、密かにか！そう、密かだ。今運営さんからヒントがね、降ってきました。「密かにですからね」って言われた。
All of them? Ah, secretly! Right, it's a secret. Management just dropped a hint: "Because it's a secret, you know."
じゃあファッションセンスかな？
Then maybe fashion sense?
いや、待って。え、なんだろう？ファッションセンス？
Wait. Eh, what could it be? Fashion sense?
え、これ間違えたらライブできない？
Eh, can't I do live streams if I get this wrong?
だめ？だめか。いや、ファッ
No? No way. Well, fash—
え、なんかやだ。自分がオシャレですって言ってるみたいでやだけど。
Eh, somehow I hate this. It sounds like I'm saying I'm stylish, which I hate, but...
いやでも、多分ファッションセンスかな？ファッションセンス！
Well, but, probably fashion sense? Fashion sense!
え、いいんですかって聞いて、何？オシャレじゃないって言いたいんですか？
Eh, when I asked if that's okay, what? Are you trying to say I'm not stylish?
ファッションセンス！
Fashion sense!
え！？なんで、なんで落とすの！？
Eh?! Why, why are you dropping me?!
落とされたんだけど！落とされた！ひどい！女子力くん？
I got dropped! I was dropped! How terrible! Girlish charm?
え、なんかこれコメントもらってるんですか？
Eh, did you get comments about this?
コメントもらってます？密かに。
Did you get comments? Secretly.
ひどい！落とされてよみんな！落とされない！
How terrible! Everyone's getting dropped! Don't drop me!
え、スバルちゃんそうなの？密かにころね女子力くん？
Eh, is that right, Subaru-chan? Secretly Korone's girlish charm?
へー、なんか、あれだね。本当に密かなんだね。
Huh, well, you know. It really is a secret.
あ、ころね、あの、あ、なんかねスバルちゃんのコメントでね、気遣いの鬼って言ってたそうです。
Ah, Korone, um, ah, apparently in Subaru-chan's comment, she said Korone is a demon of thoughtfulness.
スバルちゃんありがとーーー！ありがとねスバルちゃん！
Subaru-chan, thank you so much! Thank you, Subaru-chan!
え、じゃあ次の問題いこうかな。
Well then, let's go to the next question.
え、じゃあ次の問題、かもーん！
Eh, well then, the next question, c'mon!
あ、みおしゃだ、みおしゃ。
Ah, it's Mio-sha, Mio-sha.
え、ちょっと待って、長いいよ！
Eh, wait a second, this is long!
2019年7月25日に行われた、ミオさんところねさんのコラボ「どうぶつタワーバトル」で20個以上を積みあげる熱戦がありました。最後にころねが積みあげた動物で、崩れてしまいます。さて最後に積み上げた動物はなんだったでしょうか？
On July 25, 2019, in the "Animal Tower Battle" collab between Mio-san and Korone-san, there was a fierce battle stacking over 20 animals. Finally, the animal Korone stacked causes it to collapse. Now, what was the last animal stacked?
分かるか、ぼけー！え、ミオしゃはこれ、もう知ってるからクイズ出したんだよねな。
How would I know, you idiot! Eh, Mio-sha already knows this since she made the quiz, right?
え、なんだっけこれ？え、多分ね、シロクマじゃなかった気がする。シロクマはなし、シロクマはなしだな。
Eh, what was it again? Eh, I feel like it probably wasn't a polar bear. No polar bear, polar bear is out.
え、なんだっけ？
Eh, what was it?
シマウマ、シマウマ、なんかね線が細かったよ、なんか。多分、多分記憶的に線が細かった気がする。
Zebra, zebra... The lines were thin, somehow. I feel like, memory-wise, the lines were thin.
チーター？シマウマ？
Cheetah? Zebra?
シマウマ！
Zebra!
じゃあシマウマでいき、いきます！いいよねみんなね、シマウマでな！シマウマ！
Well then, I'm going with zebra! It's fine with everyone, right, zebra! Zebra!
なんで落とす！なんでこう間違えて落とすん！
Why drop me?! Why drop me just because I got it wrong?!
え、チーター？チーターだっけ？
Eh, cheetah? Was it a cheetah?
そう、これはね、でもよく覚えてる。あの、ミオしゃがね、あの、いてね、あの、あのあれだ、あれだったんだよ、なんだけっけ？オンラインで対戦したんだけど、ミオしゃにこうやってペーンってね、ビンタしたらミオしゃが「痛いっ」ていう回だった気がする。
That's right, I remember this well. Mio-sha was there, and... we played online, and when I slapped Mio-sha like "bam!", Mio-sha went "Ouch!", I feel like that was the episode.
気になる方、多分アーカイブはあるので、よかったら遡ってみてみてください。よろしくね！多分そんな回だった気がする。
For those who are curious, the archive should be available, so please go back and check it out if you like. Best regards! I feel like it was that kind of episode.
えみょうさん、ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much, Emyo-san!
ありがとうねみょうさん、ありがとう！
Thank you so much, Emyo-san, thank you!
じゃ次の問題いこうかな
Now, let's move on to the next question.
え、いいですか、おえさん？
Eh, is that okay, Oe-san?
早すぎる？
Too fast?
全然正解してないですねって言われた
They told me, "You're not getting any right at all."
うるせえ！
Shut up!
じゃ次の問題カモン！
Now, next question, come on!
とある相談中、『もしかしたら、ころね先輩に迷惑がかかっちゃうかもしれない…』
During a consultation, when she said, "Maybe I might cause trouble for Korone-senpai..."
という発言に対して答えたイケメンすぎる返答は以下のうちどれ？
what was the hyper-cool response given? Which of the following?
① お前にかけられる迷惑ならご褒美だ
① If it's trouble you cause me, it's a reward!
③ うるせえ口を塞いでやるぜ…（ちゅ
③ I'll shut that noisy mouth of yours... (chu)
② それで友達一人守れるなら本望だ
② If I can protect one friend with that, I'm content!
④ とりあえず朝までゲームしよー
④ For now, let's play games until morning!
え、ちょっと待って恥ずかしいよラミィちゃん、ちょっと
Eh, wait a second, that's embarrassing, Lamy-chan, hold on!
ラミィちゃん恥ずかしいよちょっと！これ覚えて
Lamy-chan, that's embarrassing, wait! Remember this...
えっと、あの、これはね、あのまあ覚えてますから
Um, well, I remember this, so...
えっと…ちょっと待って、今なんか再現してって言われた
Um... wait a second, they just told me to reenact it...
地獄なんですけど
Which is absolute hell!
じゃあ…それて友達一人守れるなら、本望だ
So... "If I can protect one friend with that, I'm content."
もうこういう空気にするじゃん絶対！えじゃないんだよ
You always turn the atmosphere into this! It's not "yay"!
じゃこれ！2番！あ、違う！2番2番！
So this! Number 2! Ah, no! Number 2, number 2!
それて友達一人守れるならってやつ、お願いします！
"If I can protect one friend with that," please!
当たりだねこれ
Is this correct?
あ、よしよしよしよし
Ah, yay, yay, yay, yay!
イエーイ！
Yay!
やめてよ！外と、撮らないで、ちょっとやめて
Stop it! Don't film outside, wait, stop!
撮らないで、やめて、寄らないで！
Don't film, stop, don't zoom in!
寄らないでよ！ラミィちゃんありがとう
Don't zoom in! Lamy-chan, thank you.
あの、その悩みの時はさ、あの、頼ってくれて嬉しかった。本当にありがとうねラミィちゃん。
When you had those worries, you relied on me, and I was so happy. Thank you so much, Lamy-chan.
あの、コラボもしようねまた！ありがとねラミィちゃん！
Let's do a collab again! Thank you so much, Lamy-chan!
恥ずかしいなちょっと、やだ
It's a bit embarrassing, no way!
「なんでその言葉かけたか？」って言われた今
They just asked, "Why did you say those words?"
「なんでかけたか？」え、でも、ラミィちゃんが初期で、あの、あのラミィちゃんに気を使ってほしくなかったから、あの「もっといいんだよ」っていう意味を込めてね、その言葉を言いました。
"Why did I say it?" Well, Lamy-chan early on, I didn't want Lamy-chan to hold back around me, so I put the meaning of "It's okay to be more yourself" into those words.
なんで落とすんだよ！ライン落とすなよ！
Why are you dropping me?! Don't drop me like that!
ちょっと遊ばれてる気がする、ちょっと
I feel like I'm being played with, a bit.
でも戻るの大変なんだからねこれ！ちょっと意味もなく落とすのやめてください！
But getting back up is so hard! Please stop dropping me for no reason!
はい、じゃ次の問題！まだある？まだあるかな？ある！じゃ次の問題カモン！
Okay, then the next question! Is there more? Are there more? Yes! Then next question, come on!
ころねの家にお泊りしたときに、ころねらしいなぁと感動した瞬間はどれでしょう！
When staying over at Korone's house, which moment made you think "That's so Korone" and moved you?
①目が覚めたら配信していた瞬間　③目覚まし時計が妖怪ウォッチだった瞬間
① The moment I woke up to find her streaming. ③ The moment her alarm clock was Yo-kai Watch.
②一緒のお布団では寝てくれなかった瞬間　④ブラウザが大量に開かれていた瞬間
② The moment she wouldn't sleep in the same futon. ④ The moment a massive number of browser tabs were open.
え、待って、どれ？え、だって、①はないんだよね？①はない
Eh, wait, which? Eh, because, ① isn't it, right? ① is out.
目が覚めたら配信していた瞬間は、ない
The moment I woke up to find her streaming — isn't it.
妖怪ウォッチだったのもたぶん殴って
Yo-kai Watch one was probably... punched?
え、④かな？え、④かな？みんなが④て言うから④にしてみよう
Eh, is it ④? Is it ④? Everyone says ④, so let's make it ④.
これ！④番のブラウザが大量に開かれていた瞬間！
This! ④ The moment a massive amount of browser tabs were open!
え、全部？全部正解？
Eh, all of them? All correct?
なんで落とすのしかも！え、全部ってどういうこと？
Why drop me on top of that?! Eh, what do you mean "all"?
え、今の問題、ぜ、全部当たりだったってこと？
Eh, does that mean the last question, all of them were correct?
全部当たってて…なんでそれみこみみこ！ちょっとおかしいよそれ！
All were correct... why is that, Miko Miko?! That's weird!
え、今のじゃころねはさ、間違いになるってこと？
Eh, so that means Korone got it wrong?
ちょっとグルだよこれ運営さんとみこみみこ！グルになっとる！
This is a colluded scam between management and Miko Miko! You guys colluded!
間違いにカウントされるらしいです。
Apparently it counts as a mistake.
ちょっと待って、おねだりしてみよう可愛く。おえさん、当たりにしてください！
Wait, let's try begging cutely. Oe-san, make it correct!
ダメみたいだね。なんか、やっぱ可愛くふるのは良くないみたいだ。じゃ次の問題！
Seems like no good. It seems like acting cute isn't good after all. Now, next question!
次の問題は、カモン！
The next question is, come on!
ころねちゃんの誕生日ケーキのかぶりものに乗っているブルーベリーの数は何個でしょうか？（見える範囲で）
How many blueberries are on Korone's birthday cake headpiece? (Within visible range)
え、ころねちゃんの誕生日ケーキのかぶりものに乗っているブルーベリーの数は何個でしょうか？
Eh, how many blueberries are on Korone's birthday cake headpiece?
ブルーベリーの数？
The number of blueberries?
ブルーベリー…え、みんな分かる？
Blueberries... Uh, does everyone know?
ねえ、分かる？ママからクイズ来たって思って喜んだのも束の間、ブルーベリーの数。
Hey, do you know? Just when I was thrilled thinking I got a quiz from Mama... the number of blueberries.
何個？
How many?
7個、7個に選択肢ないんだって。
7? There's no 7 in the choices.
え、12個？え、10個かな？
Uh, 12? Um, 10 maybe?
8個？
8?
10個か12個だ。
10 or 12.
なあきっと、19個もなかった気がする。
Nah, I'm pretty sure there weren't 19.
ないよねみんなね？ないよね！
There aren't, right everyone? Right!
10？
10?
いや、10…そんなない、そんなないよ！そんなない！
No, 10... No way, there aren't that many! No way!
ということで、15！
So, 15!
あ、違…あ、あ、ちょっと！
Ah, no... Ah, ah, wait!
ここだ！ここだ！あ、あ、10、10！
Here! Here! Ah, ah, 10, 10!
10！10！10！
10! 10! 10!
ぴえん！
Pien!
12だって。
It was 12.
え、12だったんだ、ママ！ママごめんないさい！
What, it was 12, Mama! Mama, I'm sorry!
12だったんだって、みんな12、12。
It was 12, everyone says 12, 12.
あらよ、12か。
Oh well, 12 huh.
え、ちょっと待って、次で最後？次で最後か？
Wait, is next the last one? Is it the last one?
最後なのかな次で。
Is it the last one next?
最後なのかな？え、じゃあ最後の問題呼ぶよ！
Is it the last one? Okay, I'll call the last question!
せーの、最後の問題こーい！ころさん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Ready, set, bring on the last question! Korone-san, happy birthday!
おかゆ？
Okayu?
やっほー。
Yahoo.
どこどこ？え、おかゆどこ？
Where? Where? Eh, where's Okayu?
今日はリモートだよ。
Today is remote.
なんでだよ！
Why?!
じったい、じったいちょうだい、じったい！
In-person! Give me in-person!
今日はリモートだよ。
Today is remote.
え、リモート？ねえ、ちょっとタッチしてさ。
Eh, remote? Hey, come touch me.
おかゆ～
Okayu~
おかゆ、わあ！
Okayu, wow!
おかゆ大きいな。
Okayu is big.
おかゆ大きいいね、ちょっと。あ、ここにしようじゃん。
Okayu is big, you know. Ah, let's put it here.
おかゆ、ありがと来てくれて！お誕生日おめでとう！
Okayu, thanks for coming! Happy birthday!
うれしい、ありがとうありがとうありがとう！
I'm so happy, thank you thank you thank you!
え、なんで、なんでちょっと？うれしいよ！
Eh, why, why? I'm so happy!
もっと喜びを体で体現して！
Express your joy more with your body!
うれしい！足りない足りない！うれしい！うれしい！
I'm happy! Not enough! I'm happy! I'm happy!
うれしい！うれしい！まあ、まあ、まあまあだね。
I'm happy! I'm happy! Well, well, pretty good.
まあか、ちょっともうちょっと勉強しとこう。え、なんで来てくれたの？
Well, let me study a bit more. Eh, why did you come?
いや、今日はころさんの誕生日だし。
Well, today is Korosan's birthday, and...
やっぱ僕からもクイズ出さないとなと持ってきたんだじゃん。
I thought I should give you a quiz too, so I came.
クイズ持ってきてくれたの？
You brought a quiz?
もちもち。
Mochi mochi.
え、どうしよう。
Eh, what should I do.
クイズ聞きたい？
Want to hear the quiz?
え、もうちょっといちゃいちゃしたい。
Eh, I want to be lovey-dovey a bit more.
じゃあ、最後は僕から問題出すよ。
Well then, I'll give you the last question.
バカヤロー！はい、こい！
You idiot! Come on!
こちら！
Here!
ころさんはご飯のとき必ず言う言葉があります！何でしょう？
Korosan always says a certain phrase when eating! What is it?
1、さあみんなで頂きますよ！
1, Everyone, let's eat!
2、腹減っただ！腹減っただ！
2, I'm starving! I'm starving!
違うわ、これ3だ。2、はー、いいニオイ、はー。
No, that's 3. 2, Ah, what a nice smell, ah.
3、腹減っただ！腹減っただ！
3, I'm starving! I'm starving!
4、ウェットティッシュ使う？
4, Want a wet wipe?
さあ、どれだ？
Now, which one is it?
ええ、全然わかんないんだけど。
Eh, I have no idea at all.
嘘つけよ！
Don't lie!
全然わかんないんだけど！
I really don't know!
もう、そっち行っちゃいんぜ！よ！
I'm going over there! Hey!
え、え、でもどれかな？え、みんなどれだと思うちょっと。
Eh, eh, but which one? Eh, which one do you guys think?
みんなはちなみに4かな、444444と。
Everyone's like 4, 444444 by the way.
4って言ってる？
They're saying 4?
まあたまに2とか3とかもあるけど、大方4。
Well, sometimes 2 or 3, but mostly 4.
腹減っただ！腹減っただ！って言うんだろ普通。
Usually people say 'I'm starving! I'm starving!'.
え、でも言いそう、え、全部言って見せてよ。
Eh, but it sounds like something I'd say, say them all for me.
じゃあ1、さあみんなで頂きますよ！
Then 1, Everyone, let's eat!
おいしそうじゃん。
Sounds delicious.
おいしいね。
Delicious.
2。
2.
腹減っただ！腹減っただ！そりゃそれは3、それは3。
I'm starving! I'm starving! That's 3, that's 3.
同じ間違いちょっと、同じ間違いしちゃった。
I made the same mistake, I made the same mistake.
それは3なんだよ。
That's 3.
はー、いいニオイ、はー。
Ah, what a nice smell, hah.
あ、おいしそうじゃん。
Ah, sounds delicious.
おいしいね。
Delicious.
あ、3。
Ah, 3.
腹減っただ！腹減っただ！
I'm starving! I'm starving!
おい、おいしそうじゃん。
Hey, sounds delicious.
おいしそうだな。え、4、ウェットティッシュ使う？
Sounds delicious. Eh, 4, want a wet wipe?
なんかやっぱ4が一番言わなさそうな感じするけどね。
Somehow 4 feels like the least likely thing to say.
ねえ、なんかどうなんだろうね？読んだのかな？今見た感じだとまあ3とか2っぽかったけどね。
Hey, I wonder how it is? Did they read it? From the look of it right now, it seemed like 3 or 2.
じゃあ4かやっぱり。
Then maybe 4 after all.
まあ自分のことは自分が一番分かってるからね。
Well, you know yourself best after all.
はい、じゃあ4でファイナルアンサーをおねがいしましょおかゆさん。
Yes, then please give 4 as your final answer, Okayu-san.
いいですね。
Sounds good.
はい。
Yes.
じゃあ、正解は4番！ウェットティッシュ使う？
Well then, the correct answer is number 4! Want a wet wipe?
イェーイ！
Yay!
おっかゆー！
Okayu!
さっきからさ、聞いてよちょっと！
Hey, listen to me for a second!
何に何に？
What, what?
さっきから正解して落とされるんだけど、
I keep getting it right and getting dropped down,
どういうことなの？
what is the meaning of this?
いや、遊ばれてるね、完全にね。
Well, you're totally being played with.
あ、ね、お前の立ち位置がなくなっちゃったんだよ！まだいるよ！
Ah, hey, your standing position is gone! You're still here!
あ、じゃあ、僕の立ち位置が消えたということでね、今日は
Ah, well, since my standing position has disappeared, today...
あ、ちょっと待って！待って、まだ、まだ、まだ、まだ、喋るなよ！ちょっと待て喋るな！
Ah, wait a minute! Wait, don't, don't, don't, don't talk yet! Wait, don't talk!
まだ喋るな、まだ喋るな！
Don't talk yet, don't talk yet!
え、なんかさ、他にさ、言うことない？なんか。
Eh, like, isn't there anything else to say? Like...
他に？
Anything else?
え、なんか、あの、今まで、ほら、なんかあんま最近さ、最近ってみんな、二日目かさ、喋ってないじゃんさ。
Eh, like, um, up until now, see, like, we haven't really talked lately, like for the past couple of days.
なんか、なんか、ちょうどなんか、ちょうどなんか、ある？
Like, is there anything, just right now?
えー、なんだろう、まあ
Eh, I wonder, well...
じゃあ、まあ今日も、いい犬だね。
Well, then, today is a good dog too.
今日の犬だね！
Today's a good dog!
あ、今日も犬だね。
Ah, today's a dog too.
今日も犬。
Today is a dog.
そうなの。私は今日も猫だよ。
That's right. I'm a cat today too.
あ、そうなの。
Oh, is that so.
そうだよ。
That's right.
え、ころさんにさ、今日誕生日プレゼント持ってきたんだよ！
Eh, I brought a birthday present for Korone today!
本当に！？
Really!?
さあ！ころさんのさ、左側に紐があるでしょ？ある。
Now! On Korone's left side, there's a string, right? There is.
え、これ？
Eh, this?
そう。
Right.
そう、これを、なんか、なんだろうと思ったんだよね。え、いいの、引っ張って？
Right, I wondered what this was. Eh, is it okay to pull it?
いいよ、引っ張っていいよ。
Sure, go ahead and pull it.
行くよ、おっかゆー！
Here I go, Okayu!
うん。
Yeah.
せーの！
Ready, set!
痛いのって気持ちいいでしょ？
Hurting feels good, doesn't it?
僕からはドMのプレゼントだよ！痛って！
From me, it's a masochist present! Ouch!
で、でも、よくない？気持ちいいかも。
Bu-, but isn't it nice? It might feel good.
そう、この感覚絶対忘れなよね！
That's right, never forget this feeling!
じゃあ、僕がいったらね、おっかゆ、待って、まだ、まだ、喋るよ、4、
Well, when I say, Okayu, wait, still, still, talking, 4,
ん、もう無理だよ。
Hm, no more.
じゃあね、バイバーイ！なんで落とすの？おっかゆ、ありがとね！
Well then, bye-bye! Why are you dropping me? Okayu, thanks!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、えっとこれもう1回引いたら、もう1回引いたらあれかな？
So, um, if I pull this one more time, if I pull it one more time, I wonder?
ね、首、首とりあえず首取れる！
Hey, neck, neck, my neck's gonna come off!
首取れるってこれやばいよ！
My neck's gonna come off, this is dangerous!
え、引いたら引いただけ来る感じ？
Eh, does it come as much as I pull?
いや、でもおっかゆのプレゼントって聞いたらなんかちょっと嬉しくなっちゃったかもしれない。
Well, but hearing that it's Okayu's present made me a little happy maybe.
え、てことです、あれかな？もうクイズは全部終わっちゃったんだけど、
Eh, so, I wonder? All the quizzes are already over, but
多分、え、何問中何問正解しましたか、ころねは。
Probably, eh, out of how many questions did Korone get right?
3問ぐらい？
About 3 questions?
半分以下ていう、今ちょっとおっかゆの声が聞こえたけど、
Below half, I just heard Okayu's voice saying, but
え、みんなさ、ライブできないかもしれない、ちょっと。
Eh, everyone, we might not be able to do the live, wait a minute.
ほとんど不正解だった！
Almost all of them were wrong!
え、どうしよう！え、もっとさ、ライブ結構頑張って練習してきたんだけどな。
Eh, what should I do! Eh, I worked pretty hard practicing for the live.
ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ！
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
練習して来たんだけど、
I practiced, but
え？待って、おっかゆさん、ちょっと
Eh? Wait, Okayu-san, wait a bit
あ、待って、待って、待って、待って！あ、違う！あ、ライブ、ライブ、ライブ、ライブさせてください！
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait! Ah, no! Ah, please let me do the live!
今日、本当に、あ、おっかゆ、おっかゆね、
Today, really, ah, Okayu, Okayu, see,
おっかゆさん見て、ほら！見て！
Look at Okayu-san, see! Look!
やってもいい？
Can I do it?
音が遅いよ、ちょっと。
The sound is a bit slow.
なんで落とすの？え、これ戻ってきたってことは？
Why are you dropping me? Eh, does this mean it came back?
やってもいい？
Can I do it?
あ、みんな！今ね、おっかゆさんから、えっと、誕生日だから仕方ねーなということで、ライブの許可が出ました！
Ah, everyone! Now, Okayu-san gave permission for the live, saying "can't be helped since it's your birthday"!
わーい！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
ありがとうね、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
え、てことは、ちょっと猫ねも、あの、ライブステージに移動になるんだけど、
Eh, which means, Nekomune will also move to the live stage, but
え、もうちょっとタムれたいな、みんなと。
Eh, I want to hang out a bit more with everyone.
ありがとうね、みんなコメントもたくさん見えてるからね！あの始まる前もずっと見とったし、今もずっと見とったからね！
Thank you, I can see lots of comments from everyone! I was watching all the time before it started, and I'm watching all the time now too!
ありがとう、おっかゆありがとうだって。
Thank you, thanks to Okayu, they say.
やーい！
Yay!
ていうことで、じゃあ、ここにはライブステージに移動になります。
So, well, we will move to the live stage here.
えとね、あとで、結構ね、重大発表とかもあるので、そのまま見習ってくれたらとても嬉しいです！
Um, later on, there are quite a few major announcements, so I'd be very happy if you keep watching!
てことで、えと、ちょっとした映像もね、用意したので、それを観て待っていてください！
So, um, we've prepared a short video too, so please watch it and wait!
じゃあ、またあとでね！頑張ってくる！
Well then, see you later! I'll do my best!
テレビ楽しい！
TV is fun!
楽しいな。
This is fun.
わっ！
Whoa!
カメラ！見てる？ここにだよー！
Camera! Everyone watching? Over here!
痛っ！
Ouch!
何？
What?
痛い！タライ！
Ouch! A basin!
こわい！こわいけど、でもカメラで遊びたい！遊びたい！
Scary! It's scary, but I want to play with the camera!
みんな見てる？ここにだよー！
Everyone watching? Over here!
ホロライブゲーマーズの
Hololive Gamers'
痛っ！
Ouch!
何？
What?
誰？誰もいない。
Who? Nobody's there.
誰もいないよ？
Nobody's there?
なぜ？一回一回避けるよ。
Why? I'll dodge them one by one.
いないよ、ここにはいないよ。いないからね。
Nobody's here, nobody's here. Because they're not here.
ここなら大丈夫かな？
Will this place be okay?
いやほーい、いたっ！
Yay, ouch!
なんでよ？
Why?
どうして？
How come?
なんでここだけ狙うの？
Why do you only target here?
あ、この部屋にここにしかいないからってこと？
Ah, is it because I'm the only one in this room?
逃げようもうこんなところ。
Let's escape from a place like this.
あ、もう一回遊んじゃおうかな。
Oh, shall we play one more time?
いやほーい、いたっ！
Yay, ouch!
だめよ、ちょっとこんなところもうやだ！いたいいたい！もうやだ！
No way, wait, I hate this place! Ouch, ouch! I hate it!
あーここまでくればもう大丈夫だね。
Ah, if I get this far, it'll be fine.
ということで改めてまして、おはよー！ホロライブゲーマーズの
And so, once again, good morning! Hololive Gamers'
戌神...
Inugami...
痛い！いたい！
Ouch! Ouch!
なんで？だれがやってるの？
Why?! Who's doing this?!
痛い！ホロライブ、おはよー！おこる
Ouch! Hololive, good morning! I'm mad!
きたぞ きたぞ あらわれちゃう
Here it comes, here it comes, appearing
きんきんきんきんきん　てかてかててて
kinki kinki kinki tekateka tetete
ぴーぴぴぴっぴー　ぽっぴぽ　かつじゃもん
pi pi pi pi pi po ppi po katcha mon
夢の爆弾　うちあけよ
Fire off a dream bomb
おほほさま　にっこにこ　お父さん　ほほえけ今日
Oh-hō-sama nikkoniko otōsan hohoeke kyō
みんなあつまれ　元気むらに
Everyone gather in the village of energy
どんなことが　おこるかな
What kind of things will happen?
それより一緒に　おたのしみ
More importantly, let's enjoy it together
あそぼ　あそぼ　あらわれちゃう
Let's play, let's play, appearing
しょしょしょしょしょー　ちょんたこたった
sho sho sho sho shō chonta ko tatta
こじこじこじこじ　こっちゃもん
koji koji koji koji kotcha mon
おもしろ爆弾　うちあけよ
Fire off an interesting bomb
おおぞらは　あおあお　はかせへへへ
The big sky is blue-blue, professor he-he-he
みんなあつまれ　しはじめていた
Everyone gather, it has begun
いったい何が　はじまるか
What on earth is going to start?
それより一起ししし　ドキドキわくわく
More importantly, thump-thump, excited-excited
笑い飛ばそう　あらわれちゃう
Laugh it off, appearing
きゃはははははは　きゃはははははは
kyahaha hahaha kyahaha hahaha
ぷくぷくぷくぴーぽー　かつじゃもん
puku puku puku pī pō katcha mon
笑いの爆弾　うちあけよ
Fire off a laughter bomb
おほほさま　きらららら　みんなもきゃはは
Oh-hō-sama kirararara everyone too kyahaha
みんなあつまれ　おまつりだ
Everyone gather, it's a festival
宇宙の果てから　とびいりさん
Drop-in guests from the edge of the universe
それより一起ししし　おどろおよ
More importantly, let's dance together
みんなあつまれ　おまつりだ
Everyone gather, it's a festival
宇宙の果てから　とびいりさん
Drop-in guests from the edge of the universe
それより一起ししし　おどろおよ
More importantly, let's dance together
ねぇ もう暗くなりそうだから
Hey, it's about to get dark,
でちゃってもいいかしら？
so is it okay if I come out?
ちょっとね 魔法にかかられた
Wait a minute, placed under a spell,
キミのお菓子から食べちゃうぞ
I'll start by eating your sweets!
きっと もう霧が濃くなるから
Surely the fog will grow thicker soon,
ミンナ集まるかな？
so will everyone gather around?
じっと待って アマイモノ我慢した
Waiting patiently, resisting sweet things,
ご褒美を ほら
look at your reward!
ひとつ ふたつ 鐘の音
One, two, the sound of bells,
騒ぎ出す 小さいオバケたち
little ghosts start making a fuss.
今日は 許してくれるの
Will you forgive us today?
さあ 街に行こう
Come on, let's go to town!
だって happy halloween いたずらしちゃうぞ ding-dong-dang
'Cause it's happy Halloween, we'll pull pranks, ding-dong-dang!
あっちもこっちも trick or treat キャンディーはくれないの？
Trick or treat everywhere, won't you give us candy?
だって happy halloween 幼気な ランタン パンプキン
'Cause it's happy Halloween, innocent lantern pumpkins,
疲れた ジャック も 踊る 朝 まで
tired Jack dances until morning too!
だって happy halloween オバケ の カブ だって ラララ
'Cause it's happy Halloween, ghost turnips go la la la,
今日 は 街中 trick or treat チョコ も 頂戴 よ
trick or treat all over town today, give us chocolate too!
だって happy halloween 不思議な世界 へようこそ
'Cause it's happy Halloween, welcome to a mysterious world,
疲れた ジャック も 歌う よ レッツ パティ ナイト
tired Jack sings too, let's party night!
もっと もっと ほしい 欲張り ゴースト
More and more, greedy ghosts want more,
もう ない ？ それなら 悪戯 の 餌食 ね
none left? Then you're prey for our pranks!
くれない 家 なんて 庭木 に トイレペーパー ぐるぐるしちゃえ
Wrap toilet paper around the trees of houses that won't give!
今夜 は ランタン 灯し てる なら 甘い の 頂戴
If your lantern is lit tonight, give us your sweets!
さあ let's party night ほら だって happy halloween
Now let's party night, look, 'cause it's happy Halloween,
時計 も 回る tick-tack あっち も こっち も trick or treat
clocks spin tick-tack, trick or treat everywhere!
もっと もっと ほしい 欲張り ゴースト
More and more, greedy ghosts want more,
もう ない ？ それなら 悪戯 の 餌食 ね
none left? Then you're prey for our pranks!
くれない 家 なんて 庭木 に トイレペーパー ぐるぐるしちゃえ
Wrap toilet paper around the trees of houses that won't give!
今夜 は ランタン 灯し てる なら 甘い の 頂戴
If your lantern is lit tonight, give us your sweets!
くれない 家 なんて 二度見してトイレペーパー ぐるぐるしちゃえ
Houses that don't give get wrapped in toilet paper twice over!
今夜 は ランタン 灯し てる なら 甘い の 頂戴
If your lantern is lit tonight, give us your sweets!
だって happy halloween 時計 も 回る tick-tack
'Cause it's happy Halloween, clocks spin tick-tack,
あっちもこっちも trick or treat 目もくらむ パンプキンパイ
trick or treat everywhere, dazzling pumpkin pie!
だって happy halloween だから 夜更かししちゃうじゃない
'Cause it's happy Halloween, so we stay up late, don't we?
疲れた ジャック も 寝ない わ 朝 まで
Tired Jack won't sleep until morning!
だって happy halloween だって happy halloween
'Cause it's happy Halloween, 'cause it's happy Halloween!
だって happy halloween 今日 は happy halloween
'Cause it's happy Halloween, today is happy Halloween!
さあ let's trick or treat 赤い キャンディー コロ が し て
Now let's trick or treat, rolling red candies around,
朝 まで 寝たくない
we don't want to sleep until morning!
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の胸の奥まで 届くようなメロディ 奏でるよ
Happy synthesizer, I'll play a melody that reaches deep into your heart!
僅かに散った淡い片思い 笑い話だね 今となれば
A fragile, scattered crush is just a funny story now.
見る物全て輝いて見えた あの日々がキレイに笑ってるよ
Everything we saw shone brightly, those days are smiling so purely.
我慢する事だけ覚えないなくちゃいけないの？
Do we really have to learn only how to hold back?
「大人になって頂戴ね」ならなくていいよ
"Grow up properly," you say? We don't have to!
知らないことばかり知らないなんて言えなくて
There's so much I don't know, but I couldn't admit it,
「だいぶお似合いで」ウソついてゴメンね
saying "you two look great together," sorry for the lie.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の 胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, reaching deep into your heart,
届くような メロディ 奏でるよ
playing a melody that will reach you.
つまらない 「たてまえ」や やな事全部 消してあげるから この音で
I'll erase all boring formalities and unpleasant things with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一つ 少しだけ出来る事
As someone with no redeeming qualities, the one small thing I can do
心踊らせる 飾らない言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
is convey my unembellished feelings with this electronic sound.
好きになる事 理由なんじゃなくて 「こじつけ」なんていらないんじゃない?
Falling in love isn't about reasons; you don't need far-fetched excuses, right?
時代のせいと 諦めたらそこまで 踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
If you give up blaming the times, that's it; unless you take a step, nothing begins.
「ゴメンね夜遅く 寝るところだったでしょ?」 「驚いた 私もかけようとしてた」
"Sorry for calling so late, were you going to bed?" "I'm surprised, I was about to call you too."
心の裏側をくすぐられているような 惹かれ合う2人に 幸せな音を
Like being tickled deep in our hearts, bringing a happy sound to two people drawn to each other.
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほらね 楽しくなるよ
Happy synthesizer, see how everything's enjoyable?
涙拭うメロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody to wipe away your tears.
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない? 別に 自分に素直になればいい
Don't go pretending you're stronger; just be true to your feelings inside.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一つ 少しだけ出来る事
As someone with no redeeming qualities, the one small thing I can do
ちょっと照れるような 単純な気持ち 電子音で伝えるよ
is send this simple, slightly embarrassing feeling through electronic sound.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の 胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, reaching deep into your heart,
届くような メロディ 奏でるよ
playing a melody that will reach you.
つまらない 「たてまえ」や やな事全部
I'll erase all boring formalities
消してあげるから この音で
and unpleasant things with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一つ 少しだけ出来る事
As someone with no redeeming qualities, the one small thing I can do
心踊らせる 飾らない 言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
is convey my unembellished feelings with this electronic sound.
好きになる事 理由なんじゃなくて 「こじつけ」なんていらないんじゃない?
Falling in love isn't about reasons; you don't need far-fetched excuses, right?
時代のせいと 諦めたらそこまで 踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
If you give up blaming the times, that's it; unless you take a step, nothing begins.
「ゴメンね夜遅く 寝るところだったでしょ?」 「驚いた 私もかけようとしてた」
"Sorry for calling so late, were you going to bed?" "I'm surprised, I was about to call you too."
心の裏側をくすぐられているような 惹かれ合う2人に 幸せな音を
Like being tickled deep in our hearts, bringing a happy sound to two people drawn to each other.
ハッピーシンセサイザ ほらね 楽しくなるよ
Happy synthesizer, see how everything's enjoyable?
涙拭うメロディ 奏でるよ
I'll play a melody to wipe away your tears.
強がらなくたっていいんじゃない? 別に 自分に素直になればいい
Don't go pretending you're stronger; just be true to your feelings inside.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一つ 少しだけ出来る事
As someone with no redeeming qualities, the one small thing I can do
ちょっと照れるような 単純な気持ち 電子音で伝えるよ
is send this simple, slightly embarrassing feeling through electronic sound.
ハッピーシンセサイザ 君の 胸の奥まで
Happy synthesizer, reaching deep into your heart,
届くような メロディ 奏でるよ
playing a melody that will reach you.
つまらない 「たてまえ」や やな事全部
I'll erase all boring formalities
消してあげるから この音で
and unpleasant things with this sound.
何の取り柄も無い 僕に唯一つ 少しだけ出来る事
As someone with no redeeming qualities, the one small thing I can do
心踊らせる 飾らない 言葉 電子音で伝えるよ
is convey my unembellished feelings with this electronic sound.
好きになる事 理由なんじゃなくて 「こじつけ」なんていらないんじゃない?
Falling in love isn't about reasons; you don't need far-fetched excuses, right?
時代のせいと 諦めたらそこまで 踏み出さなくちゃ何も始まらない
If you give up blaming the times, that's it; unless you take a step, nothing begins.
「ゴメンね夜遅く 寝るところだったでしょ?」 「驚いた 私もかけようとしてた」
"Sorry for calling so late, were you going to bed?" "I'm surprised, I was about to call you too."
心の裏側をくすぐられているような 惹かれ合う2人に 幸せな音を
Like being tickled deep in our hearts, bringing a happy sound to two people drawn to each other.
せーの
One, two...
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good.
もう そんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
言葉にすれば 消えちゃう関係なら
If words will ruin our relationship,
言葉を消えばいいやって 思ってた 恐れてた けどあれ なんか違うかも
I thought I should just erase words. I was scared, but wait, maybe it's different.
千里の道も一歩から 石のように固いそんな意志で
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step, with a resolution as firm as stone.
塵も積もればやまとなでしこ? 「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で!
Dust accumulates into a graceful maiden? No, putting my life on the line!
ふわふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
when you call my name, I float up to the sky.
ふわふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluttery and fluffy, fluffy and fluttering,
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
when you smile, I instantly become all smiles.
神様ありがとう 運命の悪戯でも めぐり逢えたことが幸せなの
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate, I feel blessed to have met you.
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good.
もう そんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃいらーね ぜっ そんなんじゃほーら
Yup, I don't want it like that, hey, that's not enough.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
そそ そんなんじゃやだね そそ そんなんじゃもーた
Hey, I don't want that. Hey, that's even more...
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Just look at me forever and ever.
せーの
One, two...
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good.
もう そんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっと もっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words will ruin our relationship,
言葉を消せばいいやって
then we won't need them.
思ってた 恐れてた
I thought so, I was scared.
だけど あれ? なんかちがうかも
But wait, something's not right...
千里の道も一歩から!
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a resolve as firm as stone,
ちりも積もれば山となでしこ?
dust builds up into a mountain, right?
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で!
Working to death—no, with the will to die!
ふわふふわり ふわふふわゆ
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy...
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで
When you call my name,
宇宙へ浮浮かぶ
I float up to the sky.
あなたが笑っている
When you are smiling,
笑顔になる
I become all smiles.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも めぐり逢えたことが
Even if it was just a twist of fate,
しあわせなの
I'm so blessed to have met you.
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
The feeling of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
The eyes in love are a greedy circulation
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
The maiden in love is a greedy circulation
ふわふわりの ふわふわゆ
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy...
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮浮かぶ
When you call my name, I float up to the sky just like that.
ふわふわりの ふわふわゆ
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy...
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
When you smile, I become all smiles just like that.
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God.
運命のいたずらでも めぐり逢えたことが
Even if it was just a twist of fate,
しあわせなの
I'm so blessed to have met you.
でも そんなんじゃだめ もう そんなんじゃほら 心は進化するよ もっともっと
But that's no good, look, it won't work. Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more!
そう そんなんじゃやだ ねえ そんなんじゃまだ 私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Yup, I don't want it like that. Hey, that's not enough. Please look at me forever and ever!
Oh! No! No! No!
ちょっと魔がさしたんだ
I just had a momentary lapse in judgment.
そう、僕は君だけが全てさ
Yes, you are my everything.
ねえ、情状酌量をください
Hey, please show some extenuating circumstances!
僕独りじゃ生きていけない
I can't live on my own.
Oh! Jesus!
そんな目でで見ないで
Don't look at me with those eyes!
もう、金輪際 心入れ替えるよ
I swear I'll turn over a new leaf for good!
ねえ、だから執行猶予で 一度だけ見逃して
So please, grant me a suspended sentence and overlook it just this once!
計画的な犯行の このアリバイ工作も
Even this meticulously planned alibi fabrication—
君だけは騙せない
I can't fool you of all people.
小手先の小細工じゃ No! No! No!
A clever little sleight of hand won't work, no! No! No!
まさに恋愛裁判
This is truly a love trial!
君は僕にどれくらいの罪を問う?
How severe of a crime are you going to charge me with?
最終弁論 涙の後に君から告げられた
After my tear-filled closing argument, you delivered the verdict:
僕は「有罪(ギルティ)」
I'm "guilty."
Oh! No! No! No!
最悪の事態だぞ
This is the worst-case scenario!
そう、君にフラれるくらいなら
If you're going to dump me,
ねえ、いっそ君の手で僕を暗闇に突き落としてよ
then at least push me down into the darkness with your own hands!
Oh! Jesus!
論より証拠だも
The evidence speaks for itself!
もう、僕は取り繕えないよ
I can no longer put up a front.
ねえ、ずっと君の監獄に閉じ込めてもいいから
So please, you can lock me up in your prison forever!
性格的な問題と一度だけの過ちで君はもう戻らない
Because of inherent flaws and a one-time mistake, you won't come back.
口先の弁護じゃもう許されない
Smooth-talking defense won't be forgiven anymore.
どこが完全犯罪?
How is this a "perfect crime"?
君も僕も同じだけの悲しみを 愛した人 愛された人 互いを裁き合う運命だから
You and I share the exact same sadness—we who loved and were loved are fated to judge each other.
有罪判決 君は僕にどれくらいの罪を問う?
Guilty verdict! How heavy is the crime you charge me with?
終身刑で償う覚悟 死ぬまで君だけを守るよ
I am prepared to atone with a life sentence; I will protect only you until I die.
恋愛裁判 君が僕に教えてくれた真実
Love trial! The truth you taught me:
偽りの涙の裏側で密かに微笑んだ小悪魔
A little devil secretly smiling behind crocodile tears—
そう、君も「有罪(ギルティ)」
yes, you are "guilty" too!
ちょっと魔が差したんだ 君も
I just had a momentary lapse, and you too...
僕も 同じだけの
and I as well...
悲しみを 愛した人 愛された人
share the same sadness. The one who loved, the one who was loved,
互いを さばき合う 運命だから
fated to judge one another.
有罪判決 君は僕に どれくらいの罪を問う？
Guilty verdict, how severe are the charges you'll bring against me?
最終弁論 涙の後に 君から告げられた
Final defense, after the tears, you told me...
僕は「有罪ギルティ」 Oh! No! No! No!
I am "guilty"! Oh! No! No! No!
最悪の事態だ そう、君にフラれるくらいなら
This is the worst-case scenario. If it means being dumped by you...
ねえ、いっそ君の手で僕を 闇に突き落としてよ
Hey, rather, push me down into the darkness with your own hands.
Oh! Jesus! 論より証拠だ もう、僕は取り繕えない
Oh! Jesus! Proof speaks louder than words, I can no longer keep up appearances.
ねえ、ずっと君の監獄に 閉じ込めてもいいから
Hey, it's fine if you lock me away in your prison forever.
性的な問題と 一度だけの過ちで
Due to character flaws and a one-time mistake,
君はもう戻らない 口先の弁護じゃもう許されない
you won't return, excuses won't be forgiven anymore.
どこが完全犯罪 君も僕も同じだけの悲しみを
Where is the perfect crime? You and I share the same sadness...
月夜かり昇る刻
As the moonlight rises,
灯る赤提灯
red lanterns light the scene.
祭囃子の合図
The music kicking off the festival,
ふわり 蝶が 誘い出す
fluttering butterflies entice you.
(ちょっと覗いてみてごらん)
(Why don't you take a peek and see?)
迷い込めば 抜け出せない
Once you wander in, you can't escape.
(楽しいことが したいなら)
(If you want to have some real fun)
おいでませ 極楽浄土
our doors are open, gokuraku jodo.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
アナタの声を さあ 聞かせて
let your voice be heard.
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance away, dance away, forget the time,
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
(ちょっと「いいこと」いたしましょう)
(Why don't we do something nice?)
これは夢か幻か
Is this a dream or a fantasy?
(嘘も真も 無い世界)
(A world without truth or lies)
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go together, gokuraku jodo.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
乱れる髪、息も気にせず
hair wild, without caring about your breath,
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
dance away, dance away, forget the time.
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
Tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
あなたの声を さあ 聞かせて
let your voice be heard.
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance away, dance away, forget the time,
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
今宵 あなたと 狂い咲き
Tonight, blooming like crazy with you.
美しく咲く花も いつか散りゆくもの
Even the brightest flower of all will eventually wither away.
それならこの一夜を もっと熱く愛したい
So then why not make this night even more passionately loved?
(ちょっと「いいこと」いたしましょう)
(Why don't we do something nice?)
これは夢か幻か
Is this a dream or fantasy?
(嘘も真も 無い世界)
(A world with neither truth nor lies)
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go together, gokuraku jodo.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
乱れる髪、息も気にせず
hair wild, without caring about your breath,
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
dance away, dance away, forget the time.
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
Tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
(嘘も真も 無い世界)
(A world with neither truth nor lies)
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go together, gokuraku jodo.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
あなたの声を さあ 聞かせて
let your voice be heard.
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance away, dance away, forget the time,
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
今宵 あなたと 狂い咲き
Tonight, blooming like crazy with you.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
あなたの声を さあ 聞かせて
let your voice be heard.
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance away, dance away, forget the time,
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
(嘘も真も 無い世界)
(A world with neither truth nor lies)
ゆきましょう 極楽浄土
Let's go together, gokuraku jodo.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
乱れる髪、息も気にせず
hair wild, without caring about your breath,
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
dance away, dance away, forget the time.
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
Tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
歌えや歌え 心のままに
Sing it out, and sing it loud,
あなたの声を さあ 聞かせて
let your voice be heard.
踊れや踊れ 時を忘れ
Dance away, dance away, forget the time,
今宵 共に あだ狂い咲き
tonight we're blooming together like crazy.
今宵 あなたと 狂い咲き
Tonight, blooming like crazy with you.
はーい！
Hi!
極楽浄土でしたー！どうだったかなー？
That was Gokuraku Jodo! How was it?
えっと、次の曲が最後なんだけど、
Um, the next song is the last one,
少し準備があるので、おしらせを見て待っててください！
so please check the announcements and wait a bit!
はーい、お知らせ担当のころねだよ！
Hi, it's Korone in charge of announcements!
最後の曲の前にグッズのお知らせだよ。
Before the last song, here's some merchandise news.
戌神ころね誕生日記念グッズが出ます！
Inugami Korone's birthday goods are out!
グッズは全部で4種類。
There are 4 types of goods in total.
まずは、なもり先生描き下ろしのBIGアクリルスタンド！
First, the BIG acrylic stand illustrated by Namori-sensei!
制服もなもり先生に考えていただきました。すごいかわいいです。
Namori-sensei also designed the uniform. It's super cute.
続いて、細田よ先生描き下ろしのマフラータオル＆ステッカーセット！
Next, the muffler towel & sticker set by Hosoda Yo-sensei!
ライブで使ってもいいし、野球観戦に使ってもいいのでよろしくお願いします。
You can use it at lives or baseball games, so please check it out.
続いては、ころねとあそろっちマグカップ＆獅子唐ティースプーンです！
Next is the Korone & Asorocchi mug & chili pepper teaspoon!
これはころねも配信で使ってるからみんな知ってるよね。完全にころねとあそろっちなので、持っていたらなんか多分気分がいいと思うと思います。
Korone uses this on stream so everyone knows. It's totally Korone and Asorocchi, so having it will probably make you feel good.
最後は、ころねすきーとピキピキピーマンのピンバッチ！
Last is the Koronesky & Pikipiki Piman pin badge!
これを付けてれば、みんなピキピキころねすきーだみたいな感じです。
If you wear this, it's like everyone is a Pikipiki Koronesky.
フルセットで購入してくれたお兄ちゃんには、今回限定の特別サインがついているポストカードとミニありがとうボイスがついてきます！
Brothers who buy the full set get a limited autograph postcard and mini thank-you voice!
こんなグッズはこのあと10時から販売開始ですのでよろしくね！
These goods go on sale after 10:00, so please look forward to it!
はい、たぶん最後の歌の準備が整っていると思うので、ライブ会場にお返しします！
Yeah, I think preparations for the last song are ready, so let's head back to the live venue!
みんなで呼んでみよう！せーの、ころさーん！
Let's all call her together! Ready, set, Korone-san!
じゃーん！これはなんの衣装でしょう！
Ta-da! What outfit is this?
そう！折り曲のドレスです！
That's right! It's the original song dress!
100万人記念で作ってもらちゃいました！かわいいよね！
They made it for my 1 million subscriber milestone! Isn't it cute?
いえーい！
Yay!
このライブが終わってから、10時、10時15分ぐらいからかな？メンバー限定配信でこのドレスの撮影会があるので、よかったらそちらも観に来てね。
After this live ends, around 10:00 or 10:15? There's a member-only stream photoshoot for this dress, so come check it out.
さっきお知らせにあったグッズはこのあと10時から販売開始ですので、よろしくね。
The goods announced earlier go on sale after 10:00, so please check them out.
ということで、この衣装を着ているということは、何を歌うかわかるよね？
So, wearing this outfit means you know what song we're singing, right?
では、最後の曲聞いてください！ころねの最強天才ワンダフルワールド！
Now, please listen to the final song! Korone's Strongest Genius Wonderful World!
おぁよ〜！ころねすきー
Ohayou~! Koronesky,
ゆびゆび〜！ ゆびちょうだい！
yubi yubi~! Give me your fingers!
ねぇねぇ、なんでそんなに他の子のこと詳しいの？
Hey hey, why are you so familiar with other girls?
あぁそっか、よその配信にも入り浸ってんだね、
Ah, I see, you're hanging out in everyone else's streams too,
みんな、いいんだよ、ころねは
everyone, it's fine, Korone
全然気にしてないからね！パン屋さんの
doesn't mind at all! Sneaking food at the bakery,
盗み食い配信、チャンネルの掛け持ち配信
multi-tasking streams,
ご奉仕の圧かけ改心、ねぇずっと見ていてね？
pressuring you to reform, hey keep watching me forever, okay?
そろそろ始まるよ、遅刻は厳禁！さぁ！みんな準備はおっけー？
It's about to start, tardiness is strictly prohibited! Now! Is everyone ready?
Hey guys! あーゆーれでぃ！？ゆびゆび〜！
Hey guys! Are you ready!? Yubi yubi~!
It's しょーたーいむ！！！
It's showtime!!!
奇跡的 刺激的な わんだふる最凶天災パーリない！
Miraculous, stimulating, wonderful, strongest genius party night!
空気読んだら窒息 ほら深呼吸 みんなとのお約束
If you read the air, you'll suffocate, take a deep breath, our promise together.
圧力×愛情全開＝ハッピータイム 宇宙規模の大絶叫 もうぎゅっとぎゅっとハートつかんだちゃうよ？
Pressure x full love = happy time, cosmic-scale screaming, hugging and grabbing your heart tightly, okay?
寝落ちはピキピキピーマン 絶対やだ！許さない！156cmの身長
Falling asleep is a twitchy bell pepper, absolutely no! I won't forgive you! 156cm height.
キャバリア キング チャールズ スパニエル 笑顔と体力が自慢です！
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel, my smile and stamina are my pride!
最後のチェック・ワン・ツー？
Final check, one, two?
「好きでした！」
I've always loved you!
フッ！飛んだレンズ
Hah! A flying lens—
どうやら世界は終わりみたい！？
Looks like the world is ending!?
ああ！クラッシュがまた食っちまった
Ah, the crash ate it again!
さあ来らったなのサーカス？
What kind of circus is this?
もうてーへんだ 妄想ロマンス
It's a crisis! A delusional romance,
賞味期限は最後の晩餐
whose expiration date is the Last Supper.
もうてーへんだ 胸に秘めた
It's a crisis! Unleash the grand love
大恋愛を解き放て！
you've kept hidden in your heart!
ギョクサイ覚悟！
Prepare for total self-destruction!
のぞけ！ファインなファインダ→ ワンダ→
Peek through! A fine finder, wonder—
ココロまで！ズ→ム＆ズ→ムインだ
Right into the heart! Zoom & zoom in!
ドコまでも もっともっと 知りたいな アンサ→
Everywhere, I want to know more of the answer—
ワンダ→見つめて
Wonder, gaze at me!
ファインなファインダ→ ワンダ→
A fine finder, wonder—
キミの胸の中のナンバ→争奪戦
A battle for the number one spot in your heart!
急上昇↑↑させたいな 世界の危機とか知るもんか
I want to skyrocket it! Who cares about world crises?
深呼吸 真価を問う「ずっと好きでした」！？
Taking a deep breath, questioning my true value: 'I've always loved you!?'
空前の求愛 全能イメトレの「no!no!」ぐるぐるループ
An unprecedented courtship, almighty image training's 'no! no!' endless loop.
もうてーへんだ 妄想ロマンス 一世一代大勝負
It's a crisis! A delusional romance, the once-in-a-lifetime showdown.
もうてーへんだ ワールドエンドにまさるバッドエンド！？
It's a crisis! A bad end that surpasses the world's end!?
脳脳 know no じゃ嫌なの
Brain-brain, know no, I don't want that!
のぞけ！ファインなファインダ→ ワンダ→
Peek through! A fine finder, wonder—
ココロまで！ズ→ム＆ズ→ムインだ
Right into the heart! Zoom & zoom in!
キマグレなハ→トビ→トにぱっと乗っかっちゃえ
Just jump right onto the capricious heartbeat!
ワンダ→見つめて 点と点とリンクして
Wonder, gaze at me! Link dot to dot,
ココロから手と手とリンクしたいキミと
I want to link hand to hand from the heart with you.
更新中↑↑心拍数鳴りやまないんだ
Updating ↑↑ My heart rate won't stop ringing.
もっとファインダ→ワンダ→ ファインダ→ワンダ→
More finder, wonder! Finder, wonder!
大丈夫、寂しくないでね
It's okay, don't be lonely.
いつも付き合ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for always hanging out with me.
すっごく感謝してるんだけど 他の女の子どこに行くの許さないからね
I'm super grateful, but I won't forgive you if you go anywhere with other girls!
今日もみんなよろしくね えらい？ かわいい？
Be good to me today too, everyone! Is that good? Am I cute?
あゆ→れでぃ→ え？ お手上げ？
Are you ready? Eh? Hands up?
さあ、ようこそ おいでませワンダフルキソ→トウデンガイワンダラン
Welcome, come on in to the wonderful cyber-dystopia Wonderland!
ワンダフルキストリートはワンダラン
Wonderful Kistreet is Wonderland!
みんなとナライ→一緒に楽しめるよ
Enjoying it together with everyone!
今日もきてき！超すてき！
Today is wonderful! Super lovely!
ワンダフルマイオレガニパリナイ
Wonderful my oreganipari night!
もう少しいいのもっと知りたいって いざ大暴れ
Wanting to know even more good things, now go on a rampage!
刺激的！刺激的！ワンダフル最高で最パリナイ
Stimulating! Stimulating! Wonderful, the best and most parinight!
宇宙一の大熱狂 今日もずっとずっと
The greatest frenzy in the universe! Today and forever,
はーと離さないよ
I won't let go of your heart!
世界最後の次の日も来た。
Even the day after the world's end has come.